



# Key skills

- C#
- .Net
- · .Net Core
- Web Api
- SQL Server
- · Backend Development
- LIMS



# **Technical Skills**

- C#
- SQL Server
- ASP.NET MVC
- Angular
- Reactjs
- .NET
- .NET Core
- Web API
- Crystal Report



# **Personal Information**

City Gandhinagar

Country INDIA



# Languages

English

# DHAVAL RATHOD

# **LIMS Developer**



8 Years 0 Month



rathoddhaval44@gmail

## "

A Highly-skilled and self-motivated software engineer with 7+ years of dynamic experience across different domains and technology with excellent problem solving and ability to perform well in a team.



# **Profile Summary**

Over 7+ years of experience in software development field, I have honed my skills in analyzing requirements and building quality product to matchup with client expectations. And now i am looking for a leadership role in a dynamic organization where I can apply my expertise, lead high-performing teams, and achieve measurable results



## Education

B.Tech/B.E., 2012

Gujarat Technological University, Ahmedabad



# Work Experience

#### Feb 2020 - Present

LIMS Developer

#### Capgemini

Im responsible understanding and analyzing requirements, executing work plans, coding as per company???s approach, Driving Daily Stand-Up calls, and Client communication in terms of Sprint review, planning and estimation.

#### Sep 2018 - Feb 2020

Senior Software Engineer

#### Tatvasoft

ReactJS Developer, Angular Developer, And Backend API Developer.

#### Apr 2016 - Oct 2018

Software Engineer

#### **Prompt Softech**

Software Engineer

- Hindi
- Gujarati



# Social links

http://www.linkedin.com/in/dhaval.rathod-b1631a68



#### 61 Days

### **Animal Husbandry**

Framework: Angular 5, .Net Core 2.0 Platform

### 396 Days

#### **Penguin Cloud**

Penguin Cloud is an web application which provide centralized way to manage food Chains. and Synchronization from Penguin App and provide some BI and some analytical reports.

#### 607 Days

### Penguin

Penguin is an Desktop Applications which provide WiFi Restaurant Management along with Inventory, Queue Management, Digital Menu and Banquet Management. for more details visit on www.penguinapp.in